You are blazing through these steps.
Anda melaju melalui langkah-langkah ini.
So at this point,
Saat ini,
we've done step number one where we've selected the correct views.
kita sudah selesaikan langkah 1 dengan memilih tampilan yang tepat.
We also went ahead and did step number two and
Kita juga berlanjut pada langkah 2, dan
we roughly positioned the views correctly on the screen.
secara kasar memosisikan tampilan tepat pada layar.
So now it's time to move on to step number three, styling the views, and to
Sekarang saatnya untuk lanjut pada langkah 3, gaya tampilan, dan untuk
do that, we're going to have to figure out what attributes we need to change.
lakukan itu, kita akan mencari tahu atribut yang perlu kita ubah.
All right, so what I want you to do is take a look at where we are right now.
Baiklah, saya ingin Anda lihat keadaan sekarang.
And take a look at where we want to be at the end of the app.
Lalu lihat keadaan yang diinginkan pada akhir aplikasi.
Try to figure out what the difference is between these two states are and
Coba cari tahu perbedaan antara kedua keadaan,
then write those differences down in a list in this text box.
kemudian tulis perbedaan itu pada daftar di kotak teks ini.
This will help us choose what attributes we're ultimately going to change.
Ini akan bantu kita memilih atribut yang pada akhirnya kita ubah.